# **Henry Moule**

Software Developer Born 1995 in Bristol





# Experience

## **JavaScript Developer**

CarePlanner Ltd Since November 2019

I am working on the newest iteration of the CarePlanner mobile app, which provides the appointment rostering functionality that enables carers to check in and out of appointments. The app uses React Native and consumes a GraphQL API, provided by AWS AppSync, which links it to the CarePlanner REST API.

### **Software Developer**

Active Inspiration Technologies January 2018 - November 2019

For Active Inspiration I primarily worked on the Fuell React Native app, however I also worked across the stack developing the Fuell backend using Node.js/Parse Server. Active Inspiration had many clients for whom I developed various solutions using technologies, including React, Node.js, GraphQL and Next.js.

## **Junior Software Developer**

**DYRNAN Communications** 

July 2017 - December 2017

At DYRNAN I worked primarily on the frontend, using React Native to develop an encrypted messaging app called Secoti (formerly Dyrnan).

#### Freelance Web Developer

**Candour Creative** 

July 2016 - September 2016

Candour Creative outsourced some of their development work to me, which involved developing the website nicksweeney.co.uk using WordPress as a platform to create a custom CMS (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).

# **Support Representative**

WebCurl Ltd

November 2014 - June 2016

For my year in industry at university I worked for WebCurl, a web development agency based in Oxford, where I helped develop websites using Drupal (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).



#### Education

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) Computer Science at Oxford Brookes University

2013 - 2017

A 4-year course (including a year in industry) covering Java with a focus on OOP and other modules, including Python, C/C++, JavaScript and C#. My course also involved a teaching module where I spent a week as a teaching assistant, helping to teach Python and Scratch at a secondary school. In my final year, as part of my final year project, I developed a maths game called Equation Dragger that is currently available on the Google Play Store.

# Queen Elizabeth's Hospital

2006 - 2013

A-levels: Mathematics (B), Music Technology (C), Religious Studies (C) GCSE's: 10 GCSE's including an A\* in music and A grades in Maths, History, Biology, Chemistry, Physics and Religious Studies.

#### About me

Outside of work you'll find me working on my own coding projects, playing guitar (inside and outside church), going to the gym or browsing the internet for cute dogs. My main side projects in 2020 involved helping an overseas missionary couple to develop a number of apps. These included a Bible verse a day app called Awal i Wass (Word of God for Each Day) spoken in a language called Tashelhiyt. This app is available on Google Play and the App Store, and code for all the projects can be found at https://github.com/rd113267. I am currently working with a Personal Trainer and Osteopath who commissioned me to develop an app called Christian Antonee Health. This app is yet to be released but the code can be found at https://github.com/moulie415/ChristianAnt

I have also worked in multiple Agile environments, with experience working with Jira, Asana and Hive.

#### Skills



### Contact







